libib.com 2019-06-07

# Privacy policy - Libib.com

#### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or trade items.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information.

#### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience

> Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.

  * To improve our website

> We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

  * To improve customer service

> Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

  * To process transactions

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

  * To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide when registering, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

As of 2019-06-06, we have never received a National Security Letter, FISA order, or any other classified request for user information.

#### What analytics are used?

The Google Analytics features you've implemented based on Display Advertising (e.g., Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, or Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting).

Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

#### EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield policy

See our EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield policy.

#### Cookies

In order to improve our services and the website, and provide more convenient, relevant experiences to you, we use cookies to track usage of Libib and to help you login.

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and editing their profile.

#### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

#### Terms of Service

Please also visit our Terms of Service section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at https://www.libib.com/terms-of-service

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

#### Changes

You can determine when this Privacy Policy was last revised by referring to the “LAST UPDATED” date at the bottom of this page.

https://www.libib.com/contact

LAST UPDATED: 4-30-2018
